Anthony Boucher Fanzine Collection, 1941-1973
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Anthony Boucher Fanzine Collection, 1941-1973
MS 525
Boucher, Anthony, 1911-1968
This collection is comprised of fanzines, which are self-published, small circulation magazines. The majority of the materials are dedicated to science fiction literature, but other topics are also covered including fandom, fantasy, comics, the horror genre, and general topics.
12.5 Linear Feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Biographical Note
This collection was a gift of Anthony Boucher and contains fanzines that he collected. Boucher was born in Oakland, CA and was an esteemed science fiction author, critic, and editor of Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine and The Magazine of Science Fiction and Fantasy, the latter of which he was also the co-founder. Boucher was also the author of Rocket to the Morgue from 1942 which is widely acknowledged as a sci-fi mystery classic and the first novel to combine the two genres. In 1946, Boucher helped establish the Mystery Writers of America, an organization of mystery and crime writers. In 1957 and again in 1958, The Magazine of Science Fiction and Fantasy won the Hugo Award, an annual award given for best science fiction or fantasy works, for best professional magazine. In 1970, his short story "The Quest for Saint Aquin" was selected as one of the best science fiction stories of all time by the Science Fiction Writers of America. Boucher died in 1968.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into 2 series.
Series I: Fanzines, 1941-1973
Series II: Unidentified Pages, 1957, 1958, 1961, 1965
Scope and Content Note
This collection is comprised of amateur and semi-professional fanzines which were collected by Anthony Boucher. The materials are primarily dedicated to the science fiction genre of literature, but other topics and genres including fandom, fantasy, Sword and Sorcery (a sub-genre of fantasy), horror, comics, and miscellaneous topics are represented. A myriad of printing processes were used in the creation of these materials including mimeograph, ditto, offset, and silkscreen. Materials are primarily in English, but materials in German and French are also present.
Access Terms
Fan magazines.
Science fiction--20th century--History and criticism.
Science fiction and fantasy criticism.
Science fiction--Collectors and collecting.
Science fiction--Illustrations—Periodicals.
Horror tales, American—Periodicals.
Horror tales--Appreciation.
Fantasy fiction, American—Appreciation.
Fantasy fiction, American--History and criticism.
Container List
- Series I: Fanzines, 1941-1973
  Series is arranged alphabetically by title.
  - Fanzine Collection Index (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abstract, no. 1, 8, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Acolyte, v. 1, no. 1-2, 4; v. 2, no. 1-4, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Acolyte, v. 3, no. 1-4; v. 4, no. 1-2, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ailleurs, no. 38, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Alden Press, no. 2, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alien Critic, v. 2, no. 3, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - ALIF, no. 1, 4, 14, 20, 1960, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alors, no. 8, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The American Journal of Oculenteratology, v. 1, no. 1, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Amra, v. 2, no. 1-12, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Amra, v. 2, no. 14-24, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Amra, v. 2, no. 25-35, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Amra, v. 2, no. 36-45, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Andro, no. 2, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Asp, no. 4, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Axe, no. 1-4, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bane, no. 1, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Baum Bugle, v. 1, no. 1, Anniversary Issue 1959, August 1959, Christmas 1959, August 1960, Christmas 1960 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bibliographica Futurica Fantastica, v. 1, no. 3, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Big O, v. 1, no. 3, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bixel, no. 1, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Bixel Bunk, v. 1, no. 1, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Bloomington Newsletter, September 1948; February, April, June, August, September, October, 1949; December 1950 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Bob Shaw Appreciation Magazine, v. 1, no. 1, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bulletin of the Cleveland Science Fiction Society, no. 14-16, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bulletin of the Philadelphia Astronautical Society, v. 2, no. 6, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Burroughsania, v. 2, no. 16, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Cali, no. 2, 4, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Califan, no. 1, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - California Mercury, v. 2, no. 3; v. 3, no. 1-2, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Centauri, no. 2-4, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Chanticleer, v. 1, no. 2-3, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Cole Fan, no. 2, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Colony, no. 1, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Comic Art, no. 2-6, circa 1962-1966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Confusion, v. 1, no. 7, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Crifanac, no. 4-5, The World Fanclub List, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Cry, no. 169, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Cry of the Nameless, no. 86, 91, 106-107, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - The Crystal Cube, v. 1, no. 1, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - DaFoe, no. 1-3, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Dark Star, no. 1-2, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Dawn, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - De Profundis, no. 1-3, 8, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Destiny, v. 1, no. 1-3, 7-11, 0950-0954 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Deviant, no. 1, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Diablerie, v. 1, no. 1-2, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Dianoura, v. 1, no. 1, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Differential, no. 3, 6-12, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Digit, v. 1, no. 1, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Dimensions, no. 13-15, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Dinky Bird, no. 11, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Double Bill, v. 1, no. 6; v. 2, no. 1, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Double Bill, v. 2, no. 2-4, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Dream Quest, no. 9, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Duesenberg, v. 2, FR 169, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Earth Woman's Burden, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Eccentrics Orbit, v. 1, no. 1, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The Electric Bibliograph, no. 10-11, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Epitome, no. 4, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Escape, v. 1, no. 1, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Esoterique, no. 4-5, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Etherline, no. 44, 54-63, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Etherline, no. 64-73, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Etherline, no. 74-82, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Etherline, no. 83-91, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Etherline, no. 92-101, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Eusifanso, v. 1, no. 6; v. 2, no. 4-5, 1950-1952 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - F and SF, v. 1, no. 1-3, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - FFM, April 1957, no. 1-3 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - FFM Ending, no. 1-4, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Fadaway, v. 3, no. 2, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Famous Monsters, no. 44, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Fan, no. 5, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Fan-Attic, v. 1, no. 1, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Fan Slants, v. 1, no. 1, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Fan-Vet, v. 1, no. 1-2, 5-11; v. 2, no. 3-5; v. 3. no. 1-3, 5-8; v. 4. no. 2; v. 5, no. 2, 1950-1955 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Fanac, no. 7-21, 78, 1958-1961 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Fandom & NFFF, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Fandom's Burden, no. 1-3, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Fanfare Supplement, no. 1, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Fanhistory, no. 1-3, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Fanscient, no. 3-14, 1948-1951 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Fantasia, no. 17-18, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Fantasmagorique, no. 3, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Fantasy Advertiser, v. 1, no. 1, 3-6, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Fantasy Advertiser, v. 2, no.1-6; v. 3, no. 1-5, 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Fantasy Advertiser, v. 4, no. 1-6; v. 5, no. 3, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Fantasy Commentator, v. 1, no. 1, 3, 5, 10-12; v.2, no. 1-3, 1943-1947 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Fantasy Commentator, v.2, no. 4, 8; v. 3, no. 1-6, 1947-1952 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Fantasy Fiction Field, v. 6, no. 95, 203, 1942-1944 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - The Fantasy Field, v.1, no. 1-2, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Fantasy Jackass, no. 1, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Fantasy News, v. 7, no. 4-6, 9-14, 1941-1963 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Fantasy Pseudonyms, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Fantasy Times, v. 1, no. 4; v. 2, no. 2; v. 4, no. 21, 23; v. 5, no. 1-2, 4-21, 23-24, (Whole no. 11, 94-96, 98, 100-117, 119-120), 1941, 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Fantasy Times, v. 6, no. 1-18, 20-24; v. 7, no. 1-6, (Whole no. 121-138, 140-150), 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Fantasy Times, v. 7, no. 7, 9-24; v. 8, no. 1-13 (Whole no. 151, 153-181), 1951-1953 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Fantasy Times, v. 8, no. 14-24; v. 9, no. 1-11; v. 9, no. 204-213, (Whole no. 182-213), 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Fantasy Times, v. 10-11, no. 214-249, 251-252, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Fantasy Times, v. 11-12, no. 253-269, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Fantopics, no. 4, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Fen, no. 2, circa 1944 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Fen Crittur, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Future Fandom Stories, no. 1, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Fijah, no. 3, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Forerunner, no. 2, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Futurian Advance, v. 1, no. 1, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Futurian Letters, no. 1, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Futurian Society News, no. 11, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - G2, v. 1, no. 1-4; v.3, no. 7; v. 5, no. 3, 1961-1965 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Galac-Ticks, v. 1, no. 6, 15, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Garden Library News and World Report, 5 issues, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Ghuvna, v. 1, no. 1, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Gigantic, v. 1, no. 1, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Glom, no. 6, 13, 1947, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Golden Atom, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Grapevine, no. 60, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Ground Zero, no. 1-5, 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Grue, no. 20, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Guliard, no. 838, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Gumbie, no. 1, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Habakkuk, no. 6; Chapter 2, Verse 1, 1961, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Habakkuk, Chapter 2, Verse 2-3, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Haunted, v. 1, no. 1-2, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Hello Out There, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Hklplod Gnome, no. 2, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Hobgoblin, no. 14, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Homunculus, no. 3, circa 1963 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Hugo Report, no. 1-2, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Hydra Club Bulletin, v. 1, no. 1, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Hyphen, no. 1-5, 7, 1952-1954 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Hyphen, no. 9-12, 14-16, 18, 1954-1957 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - I-Palantir, no. 1, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - IBM Fanalog Fanzine, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - If, v. 1, no.5, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Improbable, v. 1, no. 2, circa 1957 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Incinerations, v. 1, no. 1-4, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Information Bulletin, no. 1, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Innavigable Mouth, no. 1-5, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Innuendo, no. 8, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Ishbar, no. 1, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Inside, no. 3-4, 7-12, 1953-1955 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Inside, no. 13-17, no. 52; v. 2, no. 1-2, 1956-1957, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - It, v. 1, no. 4-6, 1953-1956 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Knight's Mare, no. 1, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - LASFS Newsletter, no. 2, 23-24; v. 5, no. 1-2, 2 bulletins, 1964, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - L'Affaires Shangri Fact & Friction, no. 49, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Lethe, no. 1, 5, 7, 1944-1947 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Lighthouse, no. 14-15, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - The Loyal Opposition, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Lunar Look, v. 1, no. 1, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - MFS Bulletin, v. 3, no. 8, 10-11, (whole no. 20, 22-23), 1943 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Macabre, no. 1, 14, 1952, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Magnitude, v. 1, no.3-4, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Maneki-Neko, no. 1, circa 1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Mark V, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Masque, v. 2, no. 1, 5, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Metrofan, no. 7-9, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Meuh, no. 1-3, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Miafan, no. 7, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Midge, no. 3-4, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Mimsy, no. 1-2, circa 1959 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Monster Times, no. 1, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Moor Park, no. 2, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Moonweb, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Muzzy, no. 5, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Namelessessentials, no. 1, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - National Fantasy Fan, v. 15, no. 2, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - The Nehwon Review, no. 2, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Nematode, no. 5, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - News Edited Today, no. 1, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Niekas, no. 6-11, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Niekas, no. 12-14, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Niekas, no. 15-17, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Niekas, no. 18-19, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Nighshade, v. 1, no.6, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Nyarlathotep, no. 1, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Oakventioneer, no. 0-3, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Obgis, no. 1, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Oblique, no. 4, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Odd, no. 16-18, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Offshoot, no. 5, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Old Maid's Gazette, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - One Fingers-Four Fingers, no. 4, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Oopsla, no. 9,13, 15-18, 1953-1955 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Oopsla, no. 19-25, 1955-1958 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Operation Fantast, v. 1, no. 7-8, Handbook 1952, Handbook 1953, 1951-1953 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Orgasm, v. 1, no. 2, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - The Outlander, no. 1, 13, August 1956, 1951, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Outlandi, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Outre, v. 1, no. 2, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Parsection, no. 7, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Pastell, v. 5, no. 1, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Peon, v. 1 no. 2-3; v. 2, no. 1-6; v. 3, no. 1 (2copies), (whole no. 2-13), 1948-1950 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Peon, v. 3, no. 2-4; v. 4, no. 1-5, (whole no. 14-21), 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Peon, v. 4, no. 5; v. 5, no. 1-4; v. 6, no. 1-4, (whole no. 21-28), 1950-1953 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Peon, v. 6, no. 5; v. 7, no. 1-3, (whole no. 29-32), 1953-1954 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Peon, v. 7, no. 3; v. 8, no. 1-3; v. 9, no. 1; v. 10, no. 1, (whole no. 33-38), 1954-1957 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - PITFCS, no. 127-137, circa 1958-1960 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - PITFCS, no. 138-143, 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Ploy, no. 14, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Polestar Chapbook, no. 1, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Poor Richard's Almanac, no. 9, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Probe, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Profanity, no. 1-2, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - PS SF Bulletin, v. 3, no. 5, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Psychotic, no. 5, 17-20, 23-24, circa 1952-1968 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - QAR, no. 1, (2 copies), 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - QRM, no. 1, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Quandry, no. 12, 23-29, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Quanta, v. 1, no. 4, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Question Mark, no. 1, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Reader and Collector, v. 3, no. 3-6; v. 4, no. 1-2, 1944-1946 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Renascence, no. 1, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Report to Science Fiction Fandom: Jack Speer and the Anti-C.C. Campaign, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Retrique, no. 1, circa 1958 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Review V, v. 1, no. 5, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Revolution, circa 1959 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Rhodomagnetic Digest, v. 1, no. 1-2, 4-6, 1949-1950 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Rhodomagnetic Digest, v. 1, no. 7; v. 2, no. 1-4, 6, 1950-1951 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Rhodomagnetic Digest, v. 3, no. 1, 3-5, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Rhodomagnetic Digest, v. 3, no. 6; v. 4, no. 1-2; v. 5, no. 1-2, 1952, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Riverside Quarterly, v. 1, no. 3-4; v. 2, no. 1-2, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Riverside Quarterly, v. 2, no. 3-4; v. 3, no. 1-2, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - ROT, no. 1, 5, 1955, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Rur, no. 8-10, 12-14, 16-17, circa 1958 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - SF, no. 6-7, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - SF Bulletin, v. 1, no. 2-3, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Safari, no. 47-50, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Sappho, v. 1, no. 1-2, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Sata Illustrated, no. 1, 8-9, 1956-1958 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Science and Science-Fantasy Fiction Review, v. 1, no. 3, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Science Fantasy Bulletin, no. 6-8, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Science Fantasy Bulletin, no. 9-13, 1952-1953 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Science Fantasy Report Card, no. 4, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Science Fiction Advertiser, v. 5, no. 5; v. 6, no. 5; v. 7, no. 1, 1952-1954 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - The Science Fiction Bookman, v. 1, no. 3-4; v. 2, no. 1, 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Science Fiction Five-Yearly, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Science Fiction News, no. 1-9, 11, 1953-1955 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Science Fiction Newsletter, 16-17, 19-27, 29, 1950-1953 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Science Fiction Parade, no. 2-8, 1956-1958 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Science Fiction Reader, no. 1, circa 1961 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Science Fiction Review, no. 21-23; v. 2, no. 1-2, 8, 10, 13, 16, 21, 29, 1955, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Science Fiction Times, v. 9, no. 2; v. 12, no. 270-305; v. 14, no. 1—6, (whole no.270-311), 1957-1959 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Science Fiction Times, v. 14, no.7-24; v. 15, no. 1-13, (whole no.312-340), 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Science Fiction Times, v. 15, no. 14-25; v. 16, no. 1-17, (whole no.341-369), 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Science Fiction Times, v. 16, no. 18; v. 17, no. 2-10, (whole no.370, 378-386), 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - The Science Fiction Yearbook, no. 1-2, 1957-1958 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Scottishe, no. 41, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - See Tee, v. 1, no. 1, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Sfari, no. 1-3, circa 1956 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Shadowland, v. 1, no. 1, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Shangri-La, no. 2, 4, 10, 13, 26, 31-32, 45, 1942-1957 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Shangri-La Affaires, no. 11, 13-15, 17, 19-20, 22-23, 1943-1945 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Shangri-La Affaires, no. 24-26, 28-29, 31, 1945-1946 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Shangri-La Affaires, no. 32-34, 36-39, 1946-1958 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Shangri-La Affaires, no. 44-46, 72, 1959, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Si Fan, no. 4, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Sinus Fiction, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Skyhook, no. 15-21, 1952-1954 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Skyhook, no. 22-25, 1954-1957 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Slant, no. 3-7, 1952-1953 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Smudge, no. 1, 3-4, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Sol Reader, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Something about a Fifth, circa 1960 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Spaceways, v. 3, no. 6, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Spatial Drive, v. 1, no. 1, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Spearhead, v. 2, no. 1, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Special Today, no. 5, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Spectrum, no. 1-2, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Speculative Review, no. 1-2, 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Sphere, v. 1, no. 1-2, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Staplecon, no. 2, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Starlight, v. 1, no. 1, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Starspinkle, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Stefantasy, v. 3, no. 1; v. 6, no. 3; v. 7, no. 2; v. 8, no. 1-3; v. 9, no. 1-2; v. 10, no. 1-3, (whole no. 20, 22-30), 1950-1954 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Stefantasy, v. 10, no. 4; v. 11, no. 1-3; v. 12, no. 1-3; v. 13, no. 1-2; v. 14, no. 1-2; v. 15, no. 2, (whole no. 31-43), 1954-1959 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Stefantasy, v. 16, no. 1-2; v. 17, no. 1-2; v. 18, no. 1-2; v. 19, no. 1, (whole no. 44-50), 1960-1963 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Stellar, no. 12-13, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Sun Spots, v. 5, no. 4, (whole no. 20), 1941 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Talisman, v. 1, no. 1-2, 1949-1950 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Telephonicon, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Terrane, no. 3, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Terror, no. 4, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - The Thing, no. 1-3, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Thru the Haze, no. 16-20, 22, 24-28, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Tiempo de Fantasia, v. 1, no. 2, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Tight Beam, no. 24, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Time Stream, no. 2, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - TNFF, v. 23, no. 1, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Tomorrow?, v. 1, no. 1-2 1/2, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Toward Tomorrow, no. 1, 3-4, 1942-1943 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Twilight, no. 1, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Twilight-Zine, v. 1, no. 2; v. 2, no. 1, 4, circa 1961 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Ty-dings, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Uchujin, no. 1, circa 1956 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - The UFA Bulletin, v. 1, no. 1, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Vagabond, no. 1, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Vector, no. 1, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Venus, no. 1, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Le Vie Dello Spazio, v. 1, no. 1, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - View Points, no. 2, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - The Vinegar Worm, v. 1, no. 2-4; v. 2, no. 1-5, 8-10, circa 1958-1967 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Vintkat, no. 1, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Viper, no. 3-6, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Vom, no. 18, 23-24, 27-30, 33-38, 1941-1945 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Vom, no. 39-48, 50, 1945-1947 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Vorpal Glass, no. 2, 4-5, 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Warhoon, no. 12, 14-16, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Warhoon, no. 17, 19-20, 1962, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Weird Unsolved Mysteries, v. 1, no. 1, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Western Star, no. 1-3, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - What, Neffer? Well, Hardly Effer, no. 1, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Who is This Man?, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Why Not, no. 7, circa 1964 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Willis Discovers America, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Within, no. 4, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Xero, no. 4-6, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Xero, no. 8-9, Index, 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Yandro, v. 4, no. 8; v. 5, no. 3; v. 6, no. 12, (whole no. 43, 50, 71), 1956-1958 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Yonder, no. 1, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Zap, no. 1, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - The Zed, no. 58, 778-782, 785, 798, 801, 803, circa 1954-1956 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Die Zeitschrift fur Vollstandigen Unsinn, no. 775, 2 unnumbered, 1954, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Zenith, no. 5, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Le Zombie, no. 64-65, 1955, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Series II: Unidentified Pages, 1957, 1958, 1961, 1965
  Series has no arrangement and contains loose pages from unidentified fanzines.
  - Unidentified Pages, 1957, 1958, 1961, 1965, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)